<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Nicholas Sadd | Baseball Player / Software Engineer</title><link>https://NickS55.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Nicholas Sadd | Baseball Player / Software Engineer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 15:15:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://NickS55.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Own Your Game</title><link>https://NickS55.github.io/posts/ownyourgame/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://NickS55.github.io/posts/ownyourgame/</guid><description>OwnYourGame originally started as a toy project to help develop my skills as a software engineer and create a way to connect people with a Rapsodo, trackman or other data collecting device with baseball players who didn&amp;rsquo;t have the money to buy their own. As the project grew, it became obvious that OwnYourGame could have a larger impact on the baseball community. Looking back on my time as a baseball player, I remembered</description></item><item><title>Learning Haskell</title><link>https://NickS55.github.io/posts/learning_haskell/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://NickS55.github.io/posts/learning_haskell/</guid><description>Why I chose Haskell: After spending time learning about functional programming and its promise of being a more robust programming paradigm compared to imperative programming, I decided to learn Haskell.
There are a lot of ways to descibe Haskell as a programming language. However, it is best known for being a purely functional programming language that aims to use lambda calculus to help programmers avoid the common pitfalls of modern software development.</description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>https://NickS55.github.io/now/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://NickS55.github.io/now/</guid><description>This is a variation of a &amp;ldquo;now page&amp;rdquo; !!
Location: Atlanta, GA
Current Occupation: Cox Automotive - UI Engineer
What am I learning: I am taking a dive into Haskell to learn functional programming.
Project(s): Sixth Sense - a web application designed to bridge the gap between data and coaches (pause)
OwnYourGame - enabling players to have an active role in their development by connecting them with coaches and their data</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://NickS55.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 15:15:37 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://NickS55.github.io/resume/</guid><description>Experience UI Engineer Cox Automotive Software Engineer intern iFOLIO | Summer 2020 Maintained, added features to, and fixed bugs on massive SaaS PHP web application with 1000’s of users. Participated in sales calls as sales engineer to answer any technical questions and work with clients to find the best solution for them. Refactored frontend of application from PHP/Vue.js to React.</description></item></channel></rss>